<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concept on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/tags/concept/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concept on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 18:24:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/tags/concept/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilbert Stairs</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hilbert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 18:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hilbert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hilbert_curve&#34;&gt;Hilbert Curve&lt;/a&gt; is a space-filling fractal curve. It has many computer science applications and I&amp;rsquo;ve run across its algorithm in the programs I use before. I took an interest to it and created it in various 2D forms until I wanted to try doing it in 3D. Houdini&amp;rsquo;s loopable node-graph system made it very simple and natural to set up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hexcabin</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hexcabin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 04:05:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hexcabin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a while now I&amp;rsquo;ve had an idea for this hexagonal three-story cabin fit for about two people with room for guests. Upstairs is the bedroom/study with a large glass roof (imagine watching rain under that!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transit</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/transit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 10:36:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/transit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Transit (as it&amp;rsquo;s currently called) is a project that&amp;rsquo;s been conceptual for a few years now but is finally coming to fruition now that VR is an available medium (and a perfect one at that!). There is no objective except relaxing and enjoying the worlds you&amp;rsquo;re in, it&amp;rsquo;s just a concept about experiencing beautiful places and things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Destiny</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/destiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 10:37:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/destiny/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Destiny is a project about rails. A journey, and a destination.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polygatures</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/polygatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 10:37:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/polygatures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think most artists experiment with minimalism at least once in their careers. I know I have on multiple occasions. In this exercise, I wanted to minimize personality and human facial recognition. While I could do this with made up features and randomly generated people, I thought the most interested way would be to do them of my friends, like caricatures, hence the project&amp;rsquo;s title.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whirl</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/whirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 10:38:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/whirl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I was falling asleep, I imagined a neat sort of kinetic sculpture. I imagine a sort of rod or dowel with thousands of strings all over it, all with tiny orbs of light at the ends. While stationary, these would simply look like random dots hanging down, but as the motor spun up and reached a sustained velocity, the dots would all fan out from centripetal force, and the motion would leave long streaks of light in a trail, turning into a field of stars.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dust</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 10:38:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/dust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved the concept of entropy, decay, chaos, destruction&amp;hellip; but not in an evil or sinister way, in a curious way. When something is broken, you can study its parts — the system. When something is destroyed, you can see how it was created.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pyramid Fractal</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/pyramidfractal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 10:38:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/pyramidfractal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in mathematics, which led to an early interest in fractals, which are mathematical self-similar shapes and formulas. A well-known one is the Mandelbrot fractal. A key characteristic of fractals is that if you look at a smaller part of the whole, you will see the same same structures at completely different scales.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>