<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Particles on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/tags/particles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Particles on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 13:20:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/tags/particles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brawlidays 2021</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/brawlstars-brawlidays-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 13:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/brawlstars-brawlidays-2021/</guid>
      <description>Overview Supercell hired Buck to create an entirely 3D animation to advertise their new holiday skins for the winter holidays. I was tasked with creating various snow effects for the animation.
An exciting moment that releases the snow into the scene.Snow Explosion Snow explosion fx in viewport.For the snow explosion, I employed a few different experimental techniques to assemble it. The base of the simulation actually starts as procedurally generated ballistic paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arcane Worlds 2021</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/arcane-worlds-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:25:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/arcane-worlds-2021/</guid>
      <description>Overview BUCK was hired to assist with VFX and CGI for the Arcane Worlds 2021 Opening.
I worked closely with the lead on this project to provide all the volumetric and particle effects for the scene.
A trimmed version of the Arcane Worlds 2021 Opening.Watch the full video on YouTube here.
Volumetrics The clouds are primarily procedural and time-independent, requiring no simulation, and a very simple and art-directable input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truly Spots</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/truly-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:16:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/truly-spots/</guid>
      <description>Overview Buck was hired to do some mind-bendingly fun spots for Truly&amp;rsquo;s new flavors. I was brought on in the middle of production to handle the dynamics for certain shots.
Droplet Simulation In this shot, the droplets were needed to splash away from the can and be gone where the fruits had touched the can.
One of the difficulties in this ask was that the droplets on the can were already baked in as a static mesh.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>