<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:18:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prayer for the Damned</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/aprayerforthedamned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:18:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/aprayerforthedamned/</guid>
      <description>While most of A Prayer for the Damned doesn&amp;rsquo;t have VFX, there were a few shots that needed a little more oomph.
Smoke and Debris Dynamics I roughly remade the chest and boot geometry and motion just enough to affect the smoke motion, but not for any rendering purposes. I attached the smoke&amp;rsquo;s fuel volume to the chest so that when kicked open, the emitter got dragged with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubota Earth Anim</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/kubota-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:49:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/kubota-earth/</guid>
      <description>Ambidextrous Productions came to me for rendering a realistic globe animation for a commercial spot they were working on. They were creating a spot for Kubota Tractors, which provide a wide range of farming vechicles across the globe. The animation was urgent, and important, but the project completed on-time and successfully.
Shaders Earth&amp;rsquo;s surface was created with NASA&amp;rsquo;s blue dot textures (diffuse, specular, bump). When the camera zooms down into the surface, I needed closer maps, so I grabbed some from Google Earth at different zoom levels and positioned them so they lined up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QGS Product Vis</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/qgs-vis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 22:54:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/qgs-vis/</guid>
      <description>A friend of mine does freelance product design, and needed renders of his designs for his client&amp;rsquo;s pitch (QGS). He came to me to do a few animations for the project. Even though it was extremely short notice (not his fault), we completed the project successfully and on-time. QGS is a genetics sequencing company that intends to democratize expensive genome sequencing in the lab.
My client provided the model files which were exported from Solidworks, and told me what materials the different parts had, and how each device opened and operated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are Boats</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/weareboats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 19:22:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/weareboats/</guid>
      <description>We Are Boats is a film by Zombot Pictures about love, death, and soul-searching. It was a part of the 2017 Sundance Film Festival.
I handled all the visual effects for the film. All shots were done at 4k.
Scenes included characters disappearing, camera tracking and 3D background substituion, dynamics and smoke simulation, layered matte painting and animation, compositing background elements, removing camera moire, replacing signage, phone screens, and television screens, blemish removal, and camera rig removal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone X Cases</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/ca-ipx-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/ca-ipx-cases/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Phone case renders for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.caudabe.com/collections/iphone-x-accessories&#34;&gt;Caudabe&amp;rsquo;s iPhone X Collection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentine Dayz</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/valentine-dayz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/valentine-dayz/</guid>
      <description>Valentine DayZ is a quirky horror movie about a zombie apocalypse.
I handled almost all of the visual effects for the film, the only exception being one of the shooting locations for a news broadcast offered an automated greenscreening process for one of the backdrop. I worked in After Effects for the motion tracking, rotoscoping, and compositing. All shots were done at 4k.
Dynamics Most of the smoke and fires in the film were simulated and rendered in Houdini and are supposed to represent portions of the city in ruins from the apocalypse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 7 Cases</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/ca-ip7-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/ca-ip7-cases/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.caudabe.com/&#34;&gt;Caudabe&lt;/a&gt; is a phone case manufacturing company which specializes in sleek, precision products that offer beauty and protection. I work with them to visualize their products for online presentation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lull</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/lull/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 10:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/lull/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WagooAR</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/wagooar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 09:30:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/wagooar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wagooar.com/&#34;&gt;WagooAR&lt;/a&gt; is an emerging company that creates efficient, spatially-aware augmented reality technology. In order to gain more awareness in the market, they needed a website and a video showcasing their technology and its applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choice</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:53:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/choice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.space3sixty.com/&#34;&gt;Space360&lt;/a&gt; asked me to create a logo animation for a new logo they designed for their client &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.choicetool.com/&#34;&gt;Choice&lt;/a&gt; as part of their marketing package.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShadesClub</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/shadesclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 09:30:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/shadesclub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.shadesclub.com/&#34;&gt;ShadesClub&lt;/a&gt; needed an array of new promotional materials for their 2016 rebranding. Before, all their images were actual photographs but they wanted fully 3D versions so that any scenes and animations would be possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardiome</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/guardiome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 14:10:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/guardiome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.guardiome.com&#34;&gt;Guardiome&lt;/a&gt; is a genomics company that gives people easy access to their genome. I worked with them to design branding, the website and its graphics, product renders, and much more. I am now the Chief Creative Officer at Guardiome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vape Traze</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/vapetraze/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 17:41:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/vapetraze/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Vape Traze wanted a logo animation for standalone use and also to put into other various videos showcasing their product.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space360</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/space360la/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 00:40:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/space360la/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.space3sixty.com/&#34;&gt;Space360&lt;/a&gt; asked me to create a new logo animation for them. They provided storyboards and logo assets, and I brought the idea from concept to digital reality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AminoCat</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/aminocat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 17:50:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/aminocat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/AminoCat-Entertainment-135792499865038/&#34;&gt;AminoCat Entertainment&lt;/a&gt; needed a new and updated logo animation to put on their films. The studio wanted the output to be 4k, putting a foot forward in the UHD world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fiancé</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/thefiance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 21:05:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/thefiance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Firebreathing Films asked me to do moderate VFX work for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt4159698/&#34;&gt;The Fiancé&lt;/a&gt;, a horror movie. They needed rotoscoping, compositing, and general vfx work for their film.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoli Speedmodel</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/zoli-speedmodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 21:05:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/zoli-speedmodel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A colleague of mine worked briefly at &lt;a href=&#34;http://zoli-inc.com/&#34;&gt;Zoli&lt;/a&gt; as a product designer. He needed some high-res production renders of a product but they had no 3D files to work with, only a low-res photograph.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeyglue</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/honeyglue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 21:05:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/honeyglue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://zombotpictures.com&#34;&gt;Zombot Pictures&lt;/a&gt; hired me for their film Honeyglue for VFX/compositing and also for 2D animation of a storybook which I worked with illustrations from another artist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bell Flythroughs</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/landscape-flythroughs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:06:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/landscape-flythroughs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project was for the live unveiling of a new helicopter from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bellhelicopter.com/&#34;&gt;Bell Helicopter&lt;/a&gt;. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t hired by Bell directly, I worked with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.steamshow.com/&#34;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt;, a Santa Monica based visual production studio.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Vice</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/cybervice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 21:06:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/cybervice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project required a few different things. Compositing screens (LOTS OF THEM), the design and animation of them, and a intro sequence for the beginning of the show.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me &#43; Her</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/me&#43;her/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:06:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/me&#43;her/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The short film Me + Her is a love story about two cardboard characters who grow up together but are separated suddenly by the death of one of them. The other character, through a series of events, unexpected &amp;ldquo;reunites&amp;rdquo; with her.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onyx Cinema</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/onyxcinema/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 21:06:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/onyxcinema/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;revisited-april-2015&#34;&gt;Revisited April 2015&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.onyxcinema.com/&#34;&gt;Onyx Cinema&lt;/a&gt; is an incredible cinematography company. After years of skill and network growth, they decided it was time to re-brand and build a new website. They hired &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.thejoylin.com/&#34;&gt;a colleague of mine&lt;/a&gt; to design the logo, and she directed them to me to animate it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumiq</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/alumiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 21:06:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/alumiq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://alumiq.com/&#34;&gt;Alumiq&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(pronounced &amp;lsquo;uh-loo-mik&amp;rsquo;)&lt;/em&gt; is a Los Angeles, Orange County and San Francisco wedding photography and cinematography studio that films and edits on the same day, highlighting the day&amp;rsquo;s events in a spectacular composition. Their work beautifully captures the high spirits and love the couples and families at the ceremonies have.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asus Vivobook</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/asusvivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 01:28:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/asusvivo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project, we needed to composite a screen onto a laptop that an actor was interacting with. Another artist was contracted to rotoscope and track the screens, while my job was to create an animatable replica of the Windows 8 interface as well as other apps like Outlook, Skype, and the default picture viewer. These fake apps had to be dynamic, as I would be adjusting and tweaking animations and content throughout the project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>