<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:25:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BUCK Houdini Pipeline</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/buck-tooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:25:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/buck-tooling/</guid>
      <description>Pipeline When I was first hired at Buck in 2019, one of the things I expressed interest in and that they wanted was tools to make using Houdini easier. Before I started my work, Buck had no Houdini pipeline. I established a global HSITE and turned it into a git-based respository which allowed me to make changes which propagated across all the studios around the globe.
I converted any the local &amp;lsquo;houdini.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aircover Spot</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/aircover-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 10:43:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/aircover-spot/</guid>
      <description>Buck was tasked with creating spots for AirBnB&amp;rsquo;s Aircover, an insurance program for their hosts. Rain System Similar to the Amazon Halo Spot, we needed rain for this moody animation. In fact, I brought over the same system and tweaked it for our needs and added some additional controls.
There were many iterations on the look and feel of the rain drops, their splashes, and their puddles. Knowing this is always the case, the tool was designed for ultimate flexibility in mind, so it was easy to adjust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta Connect 2022</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/meta-connect-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:25:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/meta-connect-2022/</guid>
      <description>Overview BUCK was hired by Meta to create graphics for their annual 2022 Connect conference. I was brought on early to help with 3D design and lookdev of certain effects for the project.
You can find BUCK&amp;rsquo;s project page for this here.
Lookdev Early on in lookdev, we were trying to create something unique and interesting that had life. We explored many concepts but ultimately landed on projected light across physical, grounded objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brawlidays 2021</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/brawlstars-brawlidays-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 13:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/brawlstars-brawlidays-2021/</guid>
      <description>Overview Supercell hired Buck to create an entirely 3D animation to advertise their new holiday skins for the winter holidays. I was tasked with creating various snow effects for the animation.
An exciting moment that releases the snow into the scene.Snow Explosion Snow explosion fx in viewport.For the snow explosion, I employed a few different experimental techniques to assemble it. The base of the simulation actually starts as procedurally generated ballistic paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highland Park Spots</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/highland-park-whiskey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:11:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/highland-park-whiskey/</guid>
      <description>Overview For this project, I worked with Buck&amp;rsquo;s Amsterdam office to create a series of tantilizing spots to showcase their 10, 12, and 18-year whiskies.
I was brought on very early on the project to oversee the creation of the primary effect of the commercials. I had to make sure the simulated effect was efficient enough to work with in a reasonable fashion to be able to iterate on quickly, as well as be able to send to the render farm and get final render results in a reasonable time frame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arcane Worlds 2021</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/arcane-worlds-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:25:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/arcane-worlds-2021/</guid>
      <description>Overview BUCK was hired to assist with VFX and CGI for the Arcane Worlds 2021 Opening.
I worked closely with the lead on this project to provide all the volumetric and particle effects for the scene.
A trimmed version of the Arcane Worlds 2021 Opening.Watch the full video on YouTube here.
Volumetrics The clouds are primarily procedural and time-independent, requiring no simulation, and a very simple and art-directable input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Halo</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/amazon-halo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:25:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/amazon-halo/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I was tasked with doing some rain effects for the Amazon Halo commercial. Rain One of the asks was for a particular droplet splash that hits the product. It needed to be able to be timed precisely and generate physically accurate secondary droplets. Because I hate simulating things, I decided I would design a procedural system for this that was seamless with the background rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truly Spots</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/truly-spots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:16:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/truly-spots/</guid>
      <description>Overview Buck was hired to do some mind-bendingly fun spots for Truly&amp;rsquo;s new flavors. I was brought on in the middle of production to handle the dynamics for certain shots.
Droplet Simulation In this shot, the droplets were needed to splash away from the can and be gone where the fruits had touched the can.
One of the difficulties in this ask was that the droplets on the can were already baked in as a static mesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snap Summit 2020 Intro</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/snap-summit-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:22:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/snap-summit-2020/</guid>
      <description>Snapchat needed a tranquil intro for their Snap Summit 2020 before the event aired. The animation actually lasted for 15 minutes and was very slowly evolving.
The ask was for something seemingly holographic a la James Turrell&amp;rsquo;s artwork. I created a system in Houdini that let me take a base shape and create a slew of faint distorted shells that covered the visual spectrum to build up an ethereal image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Office Social</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/microsoft-office-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 22:18:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/microsoft-office-social/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this project, Microsoft asked us to explore creative, eye-catching, tactile, looping videos to promote their soon-to-be-released office suite that had been redesigned for mobile use.
I was tasked with some of the trickier effects that we had chosen to do, the main two being a balloon inflation and popping simulation, and a glass surface constructed from melting multi-colored glass beads.
You can find the link to Buck&amp;rsquo;s project page here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organic Bracelet</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/organic_bracelet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:37:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/organic_bracelet/</guid>
      <description>As an introductory project for working with ARYSE, they wanted to create a bracelet using less material, and an interesting design that showcased their identity as a company. They are looking into experimental and generative design techniques for their products.
For this first project, they just wanted a bracelet for promotional material. This let me explore what the pipeline would be like with them and to start building some techniques and tools that would work well for future projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShadesClub 2018</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/shadesclub2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 17:22:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/shadesclub2018/</guid>
      <description>Older ShadesClub work can be found here. Every so often ShadesClub upgrades its wares, packaging, and branding, and needs new visualizations of their products for their digital storefront.
Various layouts of various productsVarious layouts of various productsLens layer animationScene Setup Before this project, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to do a multiple-product rendering project in Houdini before, so I learned lots. The challenge was to have the same products in different layouts to have the client pick his favorite, sometimes with different rig parameters and different cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dappest Branding</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/dappest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:44:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/dappest/</guid>
      <description>Dappest is a blockchain startup whose creator I worked with at Guardiome. They brought me onboard to create their branding, business cards, and create other graphical elements for the web app&amp;rsquo;s interface.
Dappest is best described as &amp;ldquo;Yelp for DApps&amp;rdquo; in that it&amp;rsquo;s a community-driven ranking and commenting platform but focuses on DApps.
Branding The early stages of branding were very exploratory as the identity of the company was still being formed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are Boats</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/weareboats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 19:22:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/weareboats/</guid>
      <description>We Are Boats is a film by Zombot Pictures about love, death, and soul-searching. It was a part of the 2017 Sundance Film Festival.
I handled all the visual effects for the film. All shots were done at 4k.
Scenes included characters disappearing, camera tracking and 3D background substituion, dynamics and smoke simulation, layered matte painting and animation, compositing background elements, removing camera moire, replacing signage, phone screens, and television screens, blemish removal, and camera rig removal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone X Cases</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/ca-ipx-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/ca-ipx-cases/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Phone case renders for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.caudabe.com/collections/iphone-x-accessories&#34;&gt;Caudabe&amp;rsquo;s iPhone X Collection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardiome</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/guardiome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 14:10:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/guardiome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.guardiome.com&#34;&gt;Guardiome&lt;/a&gt; is a genomics company that gives people easy access to their genome. I worked with them to design branding, the website and its graphics, product renders, and much more. I am now the Chief Creative Officer at Guardiome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me &#43; Her</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/me&#43;her/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:06:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/me&#43;her/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The short film Me + Her is a love story about two cardboard characters who grow up together but are separated suddenly by the death of one of them. The other character, through a series of events, unexpected &amp;ldquo;reunites&amp;rdquo; with her.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>