<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personals on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personals on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/misc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whirl</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/whirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/whirl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I was falling asleep, I imagined a neat sort of kinetic sculpture. I imagine a sort of rod or dowel with thousands of strings all over it, all with tiny orbs of light at the ends. While stationary, these would simply look like random dots hanging down, but as the motor spun up and reached a sustained velocity, the dots would all fan out from centripetal force, and the motion would leave long streaks of light in a trail, turning into a field of stars.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pyramid Fractal</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/pyramidfractal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/pyramidfractal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in mathematics, which led to an early interest in fractals, which are mathematical self-similar shapes and formulas. A well-known one is the Mandelbrot fractal. A key characteristic of fractals is that if you look at a smaller part of the whole, you will see the same same structures on vastly different scales.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dust</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/dust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved the concept of entropy, decay, chaos, destruction&amp;hellip; but not in an evil or sinister way, in a beautiful and curious way. When you break something down, you can study its parts; the system. When something is destroyed, you see how it was created.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stargaze</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/stargaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/stargaze/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being a photographer, I love experimenting with time and light, and I also personally love space and the night sky, so naturally a great way to bring all of those things together is by doing long exposure star trails.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polygatures</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/polygatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:37:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/polygatures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think most artists experiment with minimalism at least once in their careers. I know I have on multiple occasions. In this exercise, I wanted to minimize personality and human facial recognition. While I could do this with made up features and randomly generated people, I thought the most interested way would be to do them of my friends, like caricatures, hence the project&amp;rsquo;s title.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypercube</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hypercube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:37:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hypercube/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Inspired by a project someone had done where they put 6 one-way mirrors together to form a internally-reflecting cube, lit with fluorescent tubes inside. I wanted to see if I could do it in 3D, so I did. One of the things that I noticed about the real project was that the imperfections and fluctuations in the mirrors/glass made the infinite hallways seem to warp more and more as it went &amp;ldquo;deeper&amp;rdquo; into the meta reflection. I added these imperfections to my own creation and they brought it to a new level of believability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Destiny</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/destiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:37:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/destiny/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Destiny is a project about rails. A journey, and a destination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exion49 Model</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/exion49/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:37:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/exion49/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project&amp;rsquo;s goal was to recreate M-Audio&amp;rsquo;s Axiom49. During this project I expanded my knowledge about clean topology, UV mapping, and general manufacturing practices.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/giant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:37:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/giant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A procedural gas giant generator engineered in Filter Forge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transit</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/transit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:36:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/transit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Transit (name not set in stone) is a project that&amp;rsquo;s been conceptual for a few years now but is finally coming to fruition now that VR is an available medium (and a perfect one at that!). It&amp;rsquo;s a project about experiencing beautiful places and things.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bungee Chair Models</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/bungeechairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:36:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/bungeechairs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I first got my apartment, I wanted really neat furniture for it, so I got some. Two of the things I got were these Bungee chairs that have a very springy feeling to them. They were so cool that as soon as I returned home with them I went back and got another one that night.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hilbert Stairs</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hilbert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 18:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hilbert/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hexcabin</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hexcabin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 04:05:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hexcabin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>