<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Procedural on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/tags/procedural/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Procedural on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:22:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/tags/procedural/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Snap Summit 2020 Intro</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/snap-summit-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:22:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/snap-summit-2020/</guid>
      <description>Snapchat needed a tranquil intro for their Snap Summit 2020 before the event aired. The animation actually lasted for 15 minutes and was very slowly evolving.
The ask was for something seemingly holographic a la James Turrell&amp;rsquo;s artwork. I created a system in Houdini that let me take a base shape and create a slew of faint distorted shells that covered the visual spectrum to build up an ethereal image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organic Bracelet</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/organic_bracelet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:37:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/organic_bracelet/</guid>
      <description>As an introductory project for working with ARYSE, they wanted to create a bracelet using less material, and an interesting design that showcased their identity as a company. They are looking into experimental and generative design techniques for their products.
For this first project, they just wanted a bracelet for promotional material. This let me explore what the pipeline would be like with them and to start building some techniques and tools that would work well for future projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edgewalker</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/edgewalker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 14:10:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/edgewalker/</guid>
      <description>An example project that uses the output of the edgewalker.Algorithm The Edgewalker tool starts at a group of points, and walks along edges to neighboring points to create an edge group or polyline.
A progression of snapshots of the algorithm. A frame is skipped between each stage for demonstration purposes.A progression of snapshots of the algorithm. A frame is skipped between each stage for demonstration purposes.While the look can seem similar to the Find Shortest Path SOP or perhaps Edge Network, those nodes don&amp;rsquo;t avoid current edges and have many merges or splits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SideTrip Lamps</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/sidetriplamps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 21:50:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/sidetriplamps/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;SideTrip is a series of paintings focused on two characters: Azure, a boy and Alex, the God of Hiding who travel in a lonely universe of everything and nothing. The two characters explore various worlds shaped by emotion, idea, and philosophy.&amp;rdquo; — Project Director
It&amp;rsquo;s a project directed by my friend Yuya Takeda where he frequently gets 3D artists to contribute to scenes. For this scene we were asked to contribute intricate designs in the style of turkish mosaic lamps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Form</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 20:27:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/form/</guid>
      <description>Having recently got a 3D printer, I became really interested in creating one virtually in Houdini. There are a few different approaches, just like there are in real life. What&amp;rsquo;s great is being able to break the constraints of technology and do any made-up method you want. I chose lasers because lasers are SWEET.
Custom Slicer The first thing I did is try to slice up a 3D model into lots of layers, as 3D printers do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube Shuffle</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/cube-shuffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 13:38:17 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/cube-shuffle/</guid>
      <description>This was one of my first forrays into Houdini and VEX, as the whole concept of open manipulatable data was so exciting (spoiler: it still is). I wanted to sort of &amp;ldquo;atomize&amp;rdquo; an object, and the reassemble it in a different order.
Orthographic Pathing I&amp;rsquo;m always attracted to cubes, so that was the first shape I decided to try it with, and it grew from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/giant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:37:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/giant/</guid>
      <description>A procedural gas giant generator engineered in Filter Forge.
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stargaze</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/stargaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 10:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/stargaze/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being a photographer, I love experimenting with time and light, and I also personally love space and the night sky, so naturally a great way to bring all of those things together is by doing long exposure star trails.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>