<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modeling on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://bluevisual.tv/tags/modeling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modeling on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:37:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bluevisual.tv/tags/modeling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Organic Bracelet</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/organic_bracelet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:37:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/organic_bracelet/</guid>
      <description>As an introductory project for working with ARYSE, they wanted to create a bracelet using less material, and an interesting design that showcased their identity as a company. They are looking into experimental and generative design techniques for their products.
For this first project, they just wanted a bracelet for promotional material. This let me explore what the pipeline would be like with them and to start building some techniques and tools that would work well for future projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SideTrip Lamps</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/sidetriplamps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 21:50:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/sidetriplamps/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;SideTrip is a series of paintings focused on two characters: Azure, a boy and Alex, the God of Hiding who travel in a lonely universe of everything and nothing. The two characters explore various worlds shaped by emotion, idea, and philosophy.&amp;rdquo; — Project Director
It&amp;rsquo;s a project directed by my friend Yuya Takeda where he frequently gets 3D artists to contribute to scenes. For this scene we were asked to contribute intricate designs in the style of turkish mosaic lamps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lull</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/lull/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 10:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/lull/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canvases</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/canvases/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 04:32:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/canvases/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being a hobbyist photographer, I want to sell my prints. Unfortunately, buying each print in each different size would be very expensive and take up a lot of space. In addition, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t really have a great place to put to stage great pictures of them. To solve these problems, I decided to model the canvases and environments, and render them to show them off.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShadesClub</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/shadesclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 09:30:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/shadesclub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.shadesclub.com/&#34;&gt;ShadesClub&lt;/a&gt; needed an array of new promotional materials for their 2016 rebranding. Before, all their images were actual photographs but they wanted fully 3D versions so that any scenes and animations would be possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bungee Chair Models</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/bungeechairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 10:36:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/bungeechairs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I first got my apartment, I wanted really neat furniture for it, so I got some. Two of the things I got were these Bungee chairs that have a very springy feeling to them. They were so cool that as soon as I returned home with them I went back and got another one that night.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hexcabin</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hexcabin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 04:05:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/hexcabin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a while now I&amp;rsquo;ve had an idea for this hexagonal three-story cabin fit for about two people with room for guests. Upstairs is the bedroom/study with a large glass roof (imagine watching rain under that!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoli Speedmodel</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/work/zoli-speedmodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 21:05:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/work/zoli-speedmodel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A colleague of mine worked briefly at &lt;a href=&#34;http://zoli-inc.com/&#34;&gt;Zoli&lt;/a&gt; as a product designer. He needed some high-res production renders of a product but they had no 3D files to work with, only a low-res photograph.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exion49 Model</title>
      <link>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/exion49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:37:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bluevisual.tv/personal/exion49/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project&amp;rsquo;s goal was to recreate &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.m-audio.com/products/view/axiom-49&#34;&gt;M-Audio&amp;rsquo;s Axiom49&lt;/a&gt;. During this project I expanded my knowledge about clean topology, UV mapping, and general manufacturing practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>