<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiment on Blue Visual v03</title>
    <link>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/tags/experiment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experiment on Blue Visual v03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dev.bluevisual.tv/tags/experiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Whirl</title>
      <link>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/personal/whirl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/personal/whirl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I was falling asleep, I imagined a neat sort of kinetic sculpture. I imagine a sort of rod or dowel with thousands of strings all over it, all with tiny orbs of light at the ends. While stationary, these would simply look like random dots hanging down, but as the motor spun up and reached a sustained velocity, the dots would all fan out from centripetal force, and the motion would leave long streaks of light in a trail, turning into a field of stars.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dust</title>
      <link>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/personal/dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/personal/dust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved the concept of entropy, decay, chaos, destruction&amp;hellip; but not in an evil or sinister way, in a beautiful and curious way. When you break something down, you can study its parts; the system. When something is destroyed, you see how it was created.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypercube</title>
      <link>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/personal/hypercube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:37:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.bluevisual.tv/personal/hypercube/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Inspired by a project someone had done where they put 6 one-way mirrors together to form a internally-reflecting cube, lit with fluorescent tubes inside. I wanted to see if I could do it in 3D, so I did. One of the things that I noticed about the real project was that the imperfections and fluctuations in the mirrors/glass made the infinite hallways seem to warp more and more as it went &amp;ldquo;deeper&amp;rdquo; into the meta reflection. I added these imperfections to my own creation and they brought it to a new level of believability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>